greenpanthera.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy - GreenPanthera.com

**Privacy policy – terms of use.**

**Introduction.**

We, “Greenpanthera”, have undertaken to protect and honor your privacy.

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how “Greenpanthera” operates with personal data. This Policy refers to “Greenpanthera” website and service, that has got links to it (jointly called “Services”). Sometimes Service will forward to another Privacy Policy where the concrete Service privacy policy will be set out.

We can change and upgrade this Policy from time to time. That is why sometimes check this page to ensure that changes satisfy you. 

**THIS POLICY WAS LAST UPDATED ON MAY 24 TH, 2018.**

While using our services you agree, that this Policy applies to you. 

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please, contact our Support Service writing to: [support@greenpanthera.com](mailto:support@greenpanthera.com)

**What are we?**

“Greenpanthera” is international market research website, access to which is voluntary. By joining us, you will be able to earn additional income, such as operating online, filling out market research surveys, watching video materials, visiting other websites, attracting new users when shopping online. 

Based on Your registration in “Greenpanthera” website, transferring your personal data for processing, in conformity with General Data Protection Regulation, we are operating as a Manager. 

[dataprotection@greenpanthera.com](mailto:dataprotection@greenpanthera.com), A & K International Inc,  157 Barlow Drive South Brooklin, NY 11243

_How do we collect your data?_

We get data from you when you use our website with first-time registration. By drawing your attention to the fact that you are responsible for providing accurate data to “Greenpanthera” and in the event of changes, you are obliged to correct your personal data in your user account.

We inform that registration in the portal “Greenpanthera” is allowed to natural/physical persons who have reached 16 years of age.

**What data is collected from you?**

Based on General Data Protection Regulation, we collect personal data from you – that is any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural/physical person.

When registering, the required personal data to be identified are: 

·       Name, Surname – for identification of physical/natural person;

·       E-mail – for the framework for registration and prior consent for the receipt of market surveys;

·       PayPal e-mail – for redirecting of your earned income to your PayPal account;

·       Date of birth -  in order to identify if a person is not younger than 16.

For registration, voluntary data for the analysis of market research:

·     State, city/town, postal code;

·       Gender;

·       Education;

·       Family status;

·       Profession;

·       Number of family members;

·       Amount of income.

**This list is not comprehensive and can vary according to the Manager's interests.**

**How is your data used?**

“Greenpanthera” will use your data for security of registration transaction, and, based on your previous consent, your data can be transmitted to Third Parties, which are based not only in EU but also outside the European Economic Area (EEA) so their processing of your personal data will involve a transfer of data outside the EEA. These providers and business partners assist with the running of the website, services and products including, payment processing partners, as well as  our clients who can offer you various surveys, games, offers etc. to complete. In addition, whether you wish to remove your consent at any time (which, if you do, we will ensure means your profile data is removed from our records within a reasonable time from your request).

_How long do we preserve your data?_

We will preserve/store your data in our system as long you haven’t used your rights to delete your user account in “Greenpanthera” system. As well as at any time, you have the option to delete a voluntary indicated category of data.

**Who has access to your data?**

We cooperate with various survey companies, such as :

Greenpanthera may share your personal information and/or social-demographic information, including, without limitation, a unique identification number (“UID”), postal code, region, province, gender, marital status, education, ethnicity/race (where permitted by applicable law), employment related information, non-personally identifiable information on household members, consumer product and service usage and ownership (e.g., computers, cars, mobile devices, video games, etc.), home ownership, pet ownership, employment information (e.g., title, role, travel, industry, etc.), and social grade, with third party sample/market research companies (individually each a “Third Party MR Company” and collectively the “Third Party MR Companies”) for the following purposes: 

1\. Identifying client survey opportunities that you may be eligible for through the Third Party MR Companies; and 

2\. Disclosing such data elements to clients of the Third Party MR Companies for audience measurement services; and 

3\. Appending such data elements to completed client surveys and delivering the appended survey data to clients of the Third Party MR Company(ies) for analytical or research purposes; and

4\. Other uses as set forth in their privacy policy. 

If you are eligible for a client survey opportunity offered through a Third Party MR Company, the Third Party MR Company will provide your unique identification number and a survey link to us and we will invite you to participate in the client survey through email. We will not share your name, email address, or phone number with the Third Party MR Companies. In connection with the sharing of your information with a Third Party MR Company, your information may be transferred and stored outside of your country of residence, including, without limitation, in the United States, and by agreeing to this privacy policy you are agreeing to the processing and exportation of your personal information as set forth in this Section. If you have any questions about this data sharing please contact support@greenpanthera.com or you can opt-out by clicking unsubscribe link in your survey invitation, from your personal account at [www.greenpanthera.com](http://www.greenpanthera.com/) or by contacting [support@greenpanthera.com](mailto:support@greenpanthera.com) . If you opt-out, it is the responsibility of us to inform the Third Party MR Companies. Please note that A & K International Inc  is solely liable and responsible for managing all opt-out requests. Your participation in such survey opportunities does not entitle you to any benefits offered by, or membership with, the Third Party MR Companies.

   At the same time, we inform you that we will not transfer your information to third parties for marketing purposes unless you have provided explicit consent. You can cancel this consent at any time by restoring your account settings online when it is possible or communicating with our Support Center.

We inform you that your personal data, without your consent, are entitled to the competent authorities in cases of crime prevention.

_Transfer of your data to offshore countries:_

We can transfer your personal data to any of our cooperation partners outside the European Union or the European Economic Area, upon receipt of your voluntary consent-permit, which we are obliged to receive for the transfer of your personal data. We inform that these third world countries may not have the same data protection laws as your country or the European Union.

Please, contact our Support Service ([support@greenpanthera.com](mailto:support@greenpanthera.com) ), if you want to get any specific or concrete information. 

**Your choices.**

We will not contact you via email for marketing purposes, unless you have given us prior permission to do that. You can change your mind any time and not to receive marketing information any more by contacting our Support Service or restoring your account settings online when it is possible.

**Your rights.**

You have certain legitimate rights concerning your personal data processing. These rights are:

a.         Rights to be informed on the way your personal data are used.

b.        Rights to access your personal data. 

c.         Rights to specify if your personal data are incorrect.

d.        Rights to delete your personal data. 

e.         Rights to limit usage of your personal data processing. 

f.         The right to portability of data.

g.        Rights to object to how your personal data are used.

h.        Rights related to automatic decision taking and profiling.

If it seems to you your personal data are processed incorrectly or you have objections against how your personal data is processed, you have the right to complain.

You can complain to our Support Centre or Data Protection Authority in your country or any EU country, outlining how the processing of data by “Greenpanthera”  has affected your rights. 

“Greenpanthera” European Union supervising institution is:

[dataprotection@greenpanthera.com](mailto:dataprotection@greenpanthera.com), A & K International Inc,  157 Barlow Drive South Brooklin, NY 11243

**How can you access your data and update it?**

You have the right to ask “Greenpanthera” for a copy of your personal data. If you ask for access to your personal data, we will be happy to provide it with any binding legal requirements and exceptions, including identity checking procedures. Before providing the data, we will ask for an identity certificate and sufficient information about your communication with us so that we can find any relevant data. We can also charge for the issue of a copy of your data (except where it is not allowed by local legislation).

For us your data accuracy is very important. That is why – if you want to get a copy of your personal data at our disposal, or if you change your e-mail address or any other of your data that are at our disposal, if data is incorrect or outdated, please, contact our Support Service -    [support@greenpanthera.com](mailto:support@greenpanthera.com).

**Existing security measures to protect from loss, abuse or tampering of your data:**

When you give us personal data, we take the necessary steps to ensure that it is processing is safe. Any sensitive information (for example, information about a PayPal account (e-mail) is encrypted and protected. On our websites, when you're on a secure webpage, a lock icon appears in most Internet browser address bar.

Non-sensitive information (your e-mail address, etc.) is transferred through the Internet on a normal path and, in this case, 100% security can never be given. Therefore, although we are trying to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of the data that you have transferred to us, and you are transferring them on your own responsibility. When we receive your data, we do everything possible to ensure their security in our systems. You are responsible for the privacy of your password that you choose at creating an account. We ask you not to reveal your password to anyone!

**Profiling.**

Profiling is the processing of any kind of automatic personal data to analyze or predict behavior. We do not do it.

**Usage of cookies.**

As many other websites, “Greenpanthera” website uses cookies. Cookies are small sets of information that the organization sends to your computer and stores on your hard drive to allow this website to recognize you when you visit the site. They collect statistical data on your browsing activities and models, and do not identify you as an individual. For example, we use cookies to preserve the language you use. This helps to improve our website and provide a better, more personalized service. 

It is possible to turn off cookies when changing your browser settings. For more information about how to switch off cookies on your computer, see our full Terms of Cookie Usage. Turning down cookies can cause functionality problems when using our website.

_Links to other websites._

Our website contains links to other websites managed by other organizations. This Privacy Policy applies only to our website, so we encourage you to read privacy policies and terms of usage on other websites, you visit. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites if you access them through links on our website.

Moreover, if you have accessed our website from a third-party website, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies, practices of the owners and managers of this third-party website; and we recommend you to check this third-party site’s Policy.

**Social networks.**

Some of our services include social networking features such as Facebook ® “Like” button and widgets, “Share” buttons and interactive mini programs. These services can collect information, such as websites and IP addresses that you visit, and you can set up cookies to ensure proper operation of the functions. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of data collected by these third parties. It is advised to review data privacy policies and terms of use or policies applicable to third-party services that you join, use or access.

**Contact us:**

We understand you can have questions or worries concerning these Terms of use of our Privacy Policy. Or maybe you want to submit complaint. Please, contact us any of these ways:

** ** “ **Greenpanthera”** e-mail:  

Address: A & K International Inc,  157 Barlow Drive South Brooklin, NY 11243
